Welcome to Trade with Proper Greece.
In this video, we are going to
discuss three such stocks of the banking and finance sector. We are going to
discuss their labels and fiction,
which are seen to be forming very good quality this week, the
first of which is RBL Bank. So this is the chart of RBL Bank
dam and here you will
clearly see in the chart of the first time that it has been
pregnant with a big volume,
RBL Bank broke the price range
last week, you can see this here
exactly, but if you look at it,
a big police control was formed with Bollywood,
after that the price also tested, then
again the request was my support level, from there
if there is a reversal, then in the coming trading
session you can note down both the support and near by
resistance levels,
you must note down the support level which
is 1213, this
price level is a very good support level
and when the request happened, you
can see that it was 22.35, so this support
level 1,
this change has happened, you can see the second point five
closing in this and in this
You can also take such a target on 2017, the Indian train distance of near bank
and the day it reaches the level of 3.7, then
after that the next target which is
looking at the above minute lena, 234 110 will
come as the next target, the day the
11th rate of 2.7, all these levels have
completely increased for the weekly Monday to Friday days, so that is why if
you
keep the reverse conversion and you will get the benefit
and now the next stock is Bajaj
Pulsar, you can see in Bajaj Finserv, it is
continuously rallying, this momentum is
continuously maintained and in this momentum, if
you register for it and subscribe,
which can happen on Monday itself, then
you click on it as a pimpl,
205, this is the exit poll and you should keep it
loaded in the app because Bajaj Finserv is
continuously rising very well
and there was no bell, pay
attention to the resistance there.  It is
needed because there is a possibility of a fall from there,
so all this record was
shown to you and after that
you can note down the All India Registered 1305, there can be a
reversal from here, now
after this the next date is of the
ICICI Lombard. To avoid the labels in ICICI Lombard,
we will have to go to the one hour time, which is in
front of you and such people should
definitely note down the support level
which is 1553 5155 1.4, these are very
good support levels for such people
and here you can see that this
support level, when the price fell below this,
when there was a reversal from here, the
next day a reversal was happening from this support level, the
register was covering the back,
but here you can see that a big
record was made on that day, after that whenever it
comes downwards, it happens again and again from here, it
tries to get 55133 in ghee, in this price range the stock  You
can also do it and if it does not break, then
open it in time and
you will check here, there will be a big drop in it,
so come and
keep clicking to subscribe and shock like this, in this lemon
we update the time limit here, to
get its benefits, definitely subscribe to the channel.